Military
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Military
2.1.2.8
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1430
- Military, 2.1.2.8
  - Soldiers sitting outside Y.M.C.A. “Eagle Hut”, circa 1914-1919; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Group photograph of Red Cross workers, circa 1914-1919; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Soldier with two female Red Cross workers, circa 1914-1919; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Hospital with row of Red Cross ambulances parked outside, circa 1914-1919; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Soldiers in hospital, circa 1914-1919; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Soldier in hospital bed being attended to, circa 1914-1919; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Casualty being carried on stretcher, circa 1914-1919; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Casualties, circa 1914-1919; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Soldier at gravesite, circa 1914-1919; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Explosion, circa 1914-1919; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Soldiers holding life preserver from the S.S. Lusitania, circa 1914-1919; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Red Cross ship, circa 1914-1919; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Battleship, circa 1914-1919; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Canon, circa 1914-1919; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Canon, circa 1914-1919; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Bullet ridden façade of building, circa 1914-1919; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  - Military ski patrol, circa 1914-1919; 37; 3x4 color (Box 1430)
  Box 1431
- Military, 2.1.2.8
  - Street scene, soldiers, circa 1914-1919; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Street scene, soldiers, circa 1914-1919; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Street scene, two Scottish soldiers talking, circa 1914-1919; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Soldier in wheelchair, young girl and other soldier on sidewalk, circa 1914-1919; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Two soldiers talking, circa 1914-1919; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Two soldiers at rest, circa 1914-1919; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Three soldiers at rest, circa 1914-1919; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Two soldiers sharing cigarette, circa 1914-1919; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Panorama, soldiers resting on hilltop, circa 1914-1919; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Panorama, two soldiers on hilltop, circa 1914-1919; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Panorama, soldier on cliff, circa 1914-1919; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Panorama, two soldiers resting in foreground, circa 1914-1919; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Three soldiers amid ruins, circa 1914-1919; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Two soldiers standing beside arched bridge, circa 1914-1919; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Two soldiers speaking to civilian man at unidentified estate, circa 1914-1919; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Soldiers and trucks parked by stone building, distant view, circa 1914-1919; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Two soldiers talking to Military Policeman, circa 1914-1919; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Two soldiers on wooded hill overlooking fields, one soldier holding gun, circa 1914-1919; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Two soldiers, one holding gas mask, circa 1914-1919; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Two soldiers talking, circa 1914-1919; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Soldier manning machine gun on wheeled platform, dog asleep at base, circa 1914-1919; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Soldiers in line holding water canteens, circa 1914-1919; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - City panorama, group of soldiers in foreground, circa 1914-1919; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Soldiers and civilians standing in group, circa 1914-1919; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Group of soldiers talking, circa 1914-1919; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Many soldiers standing on hill overlooking town, circa 1914-1919; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Soldiers marching outside barracks, circa 1914-1919; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Soldiers and civilians watching ceremony in city square, France, circa 1914-1919; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Soldiers on horseback carrying flags, circa 1914-1919; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Soldiers on the side of a road walking amid ruins, circa 1914-1919; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Soldiers watching steamroller on road, circa 1914-1919; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Tents set up over ruins, circa 1914-1919; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Soldiers observing civilians, Egypt[?], circa 1914-1919; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Civilians watching soldiers in ceremony, Egypt[?], circa 1914-1919; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Soldier and Egyptian civilians looking at camera, Egypt, circa 1914-1919; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  - Civilians watching military parade, Egypt[?], circa 1914-1919; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1431)
  Box 1432
- Military, 2.1.2.8
  - Group of soldiers, civilians in background, circa 1914-1919; 1; 3x4 b&w (Box 1432)
  - Street scene, three soldiers looking at map, two other soldiers talking, circa 1914-1919; 2; 3x4 b&w (Box 1432)
  - Photographer setting up camera, two soldiers and woman posing, circa 1914-1919; 3; 3x4 b&w (Box 1432)
  - Soldiers walking down alley, rear view, circa 1914-1919; 4; 3x3 b&w (Box 1432)
  - Group of Egyptian soldiers smoking hookah, circa 1914-1919; 5; 3x3 b&w (Box 1432)
  - Soldier, standing, posed for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier, seated, posed for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier, standing, posed for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier posed for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier on horseback, posed for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier, standing, posed for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 11; 3x4 b&w (Box 1432)
  - Soldier posed for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 12; 3x4 b&w (Box 1432)
  - Soldier posed for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 13; 3x4 b&w (Box 1432)
  - Soldier and horse, circa 1914-1919; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier, standing, circa 1914-1919; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier manning gun, circa 1914-1919; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier with cane, circa 1914-1919; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier with rifle on steps of building, circa 1914-1919; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier on roof overlooking cathedral, circa 1914-1919; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier sitting at desk in church, circa 1914-1919; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier walking through water, circa 1914-1919; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier doing tricks with rope aboard ship, circa 1914-1919; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Many soldiers aboard ship, circa 1914-1919; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier, standing, posing for photograph, aboard ship, circa 1914-1919; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Two men and two women standing aboard ship, posing for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldiers on train waving to camera, circa 1914-1919; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldier holding hand grenade in automobile, posing for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Soldiers and Red Cross workers on train, circa 1914-1919; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Two soldiers in automobile, circa 1914-1919; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Street scene, soldiers in truck, civilians in background, Germany, circa 1914-1919; 30; 3x3 b&w (Box 1432)
  - Dirigible in flight, distant view, circa 1914-1919; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Plane flying past mountain, circa 1914-1919; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Plane flying over fields, aerial view, circa 1914-1919; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Plane flying over trees, photograph taken from another plane, circa 1914-1919; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Plane flying over city, circa 1914-1919; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1432)
  - Plane flying over river, circa 1914-1919; 36; 3x4 b&w (Box 1432)
  Box 1433
- Military, 2.1.2.8
  - Seaplane on water, circa 1914-1919; 1; 3x4 b&w (Box 1433)
  - Seaplane on water, photograph taken from another airplane, circa 1914-1919; 2; 3x4 b&w (Box 1433)
  - Seaplane in flight, photograph taken from another airplane, circa 1914-1919; 3; 3x4 b&w (Box 1433)
  - Two biplanes in flight, circa 1914-1919; 4; 3x3 b&w (Box 1433)
  - Soldiers standing on pontoons of seaplane, circa 1914-1919; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldiers standing on pontoons of seaplane, circa 1914-1919; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldiers placing seaplane on water, circa 1914-1919; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldiers and civilians gathered near biplane in field, circa 1914-1919; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldiers seated in biplane, circa 1914-1919; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldier posing in front of biplane, circa 1914-1919; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Pilot seated in front cockpit of biplane, photographer standing in rear seat, circa 1914-1919; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldier and boy, circa 1914-1919; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldier and woman embracing as they sit beside a fountain, circa 1914-1919; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldier and woman talking as they sit beside a fountain, circa 1914-1919; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Two soldiers embracing women on bench, circa 1914-1919; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldier and girl on horseback, posing for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldiers watching women talk on street, circa 1914-1919; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldiers at unidentified estate, circa 1914-1919; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldiers and civilians at guard station, circa 1914-1919; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldier on sidewalk with two women, circa 1914-1919; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldiers helping two women in garden, circa 1914-1919; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Two soldiers and children, circa 1914-1919; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldier standing with two women, posed for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldier sleeping on bench next to four women, circa 1914-1919; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldier talking to two women, well-dressed man looking at camera, circa 1914-1919; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldiers and civilians talking on sidewalk, circa 1914-1919; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldier and woman, circa 1914-1919; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldiers watching woman on street, circa 1914-1919; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldier and two women on street, posing for photograph, circa 1914-1919; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1433)
  - Soldier holding two children, circa 1914-1919; 30; 3x4 b&w (Box 1433)
  - Soldier and woman, circa 1914-1919; 31; 3x4 b&w (Box 1433)